Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive MSS.091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Fashion Moda as a Business, 113010
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 113100
    - West 44th., undated; cuid8903; 113102 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Wexford press., undated; cuid8904; 113101 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Subseries B: Grants and Fundraising, 113011
    Scope and Contents note
    Series II Subseries B, Grants and Fundraising, contains documentation of grant proposals and fundraising projects.
    - Arts Forward fund, 1992; cuid8905; 113099 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1978-1981; cuid8906; 113098 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1984-1985; cuid8907; 113097 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1987-1988; cuid8908; 113096 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bronx Council of Arts, application, 1993; cuid8909; 113095 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Chase Manhattan neighborhood grant, 1986-1987; cuid8910; 113094 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Colorado Council on the Arts and Humanities, grant application, 1984-1985; cuid8911; 113093 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Corporations approached for funding, 1980-1982; cuid8912; 113092 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, final report, 1985-1986; cuid8913; 113091 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, letters & voucher, 1980-1981; cuid8914; 113090 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, load fund application, 1989-1990; cuid8915; 113089 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1979-1980; cuid8916; 113088 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1985-1986; cuid8917; 113087 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1988-1989; cuid8918; 113086 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal receipts, 1988-1989; cuid8919; 113085 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1989-1990; cuid8920; 113084 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1990-1991; cuid8921; 113083 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, report, 1983-1984; cuid8922; 113082 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Funding research., undated; cuid8923; 113081 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Fundraising, 1979-1980; cuid8924; 113080 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Funds received, 1980-1984; cuid8925; 113079 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - H. U. D., fix-up money, 1985; cuid8926; 113078 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Institute of Museum services, application, 1980; cuid8927; 113077 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Kresge Foundation, grant, 1991; cuid8928; 113076 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Media Bureau, the Kitchen Center, application, 1979; cuid8929; 113075 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - N. E. A., contract, 1985-1986; cuid8930; 113074 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - N. E. A., expansion arts, 1982-1983; cuid8931; 113073 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - N. E. A., expansion arts, 1986-1987; cuid8932; 113072 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - N. E. A., final reports, 1985-1989; cuid8933; 113071 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - N. E. A., interarts "presenting", 1985; cuid8934; 113070 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - N. E. A., interarts, 1986-1987; cuid8935; 113069 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - N. E. A., interarts, 1987-1988; cuid8936; 113068 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - N. E. A., arts (radio), 1984-1985; cuid8937; 113067 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - N. E. A., media arts, 1987-1986; cuid8938; 113066 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - N. E. A., museum, 1991-1992; cuid8939; 113065 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - N. E. A., organization, 1980-1981; cuid8940; 113064 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - N. E. A., organization, 1988-1989; cuid8941; 113063 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - N. E. A., panel notes, 1986-1988; cuid8942; 113062 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - N. E. A., printed material, 1987; cuid8943; 113061 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - N. E. A., special exhibitions, 1984-1985; cuid8944; 113060 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1980-1981; cuid8945; 113059 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1981-1982; cuid8946; 113058 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1982-1983; cuid8947; 113057 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1983-1984; cuid8948; 113056 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1984-1985; cuid8949; 113055 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1985-1986; cuid8950; 113054 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1985-1988; cuid8951; 113053 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1990-1991; cuid8952; 113052 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - N. Y. Foundation for the Arts, 1985-1987; cuid8953; 113051 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - NYSCA, application, 1984-1985; cuid8954; 113050 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - NYSCA, application, 1985-1986; cuid8955; 113049 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - NYSCA, application, 1986-1987; cuid8956; 113048 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - NYSCA, application, 1987-1988; cuid8957; 113047 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - NYSCA, application, 1989-1990; cuid8958; 113046 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - NYSCA, application, 1990-1991; cuid8959; 113045 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - NYSCA, application, 1991-1992; cuid8960; 113044 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - NYSCA, application, 1992-1993; cuid8961; 113043 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - NYSCA, application, 1993-1994; cuid8962; 113042 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - NYSCA, architectural application, 1990-1991; cuid8963; 113041 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - NYSCA, audit, 1989-1991; cuid8964; 113040 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1979-1980; cuid8965; 113039 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1980-1981; cuid8966; 113038 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1981-1982; cuid8967; 113037 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1982-1983; cuid8968; 113036 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1983-1984; cuid8969; 113035 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1985-1986; cuid8970; 113034 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1987-1988; cuid8971; 113033 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1984; cuid8972; 113032 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1985-1986; cuid8973; 113031 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1986-1987; cuid8974; 113030 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - NYSCA, funded presenters, 1986-1987; cuid8975; 113029 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - NYSCA, funding report, 1985-1986; cuid8976; 113028 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - NYSCA, slide scripts., undated; cuid8977; 113027 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - NYSCA, South Bronx Show proposal, 1987-1988; cuid8978; 113026 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Marion Brown, 1987; cuid8979; 113025 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Ken Garrett, 1987-1988; cuid8980; 113024 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Barbara T. Smith, 1987-1988; cuid8981; 113023 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, David Finn, April - May 1984., cuid8982; 113022 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Nan Goldin, August 1983 - July 1984., 1983 - 1984; cuid8983; 113021 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Charles Hardgrove, March 1-30, 1984., cuid8984; 113020 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Dragon Ilic, September 7-30, 1984., cuid8985; 113019 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project funding, 1983- 1984; cuid8986; 113018 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Presenting new writers, 1987; cuid8987; 113017 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Responsibilities of a Director of a New York, New Jersey, or Connecticut Non-Profit Corporation., undated; cuid8988; 113016 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Reed Foundation, Inc., 1986; cuid8989; 113015 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - South Bronx Cultural Center, 1979- 1980; cuid8990; 113014 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Unidentified slide scripts., undated; cuid8991; 113013 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Unidentified grant information., undated; cuid8992; 113012 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Material, 112471
  Series III is divided into seven subseries and contains 18 boxes of documents. The files are arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Artists Files, 112867
    Series III subseries A, Artists Files, contains files Fashion Moda kept on their artists and exhibitions including: resumes, exhibition proposals, plans for exhibitions, consignment forms, program reports, and production materials for exhibitions. Please note that not all of the artists included here actually showed at Fashion Moda.
    - Access Bronx., undated; cuid8993; 113009 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - African Caribbean poetry theater, June 27, 1987., cuid8994; 113008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Agent, announcement., undated; cuid8995; 113007 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated; cuid8996; 113006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - American Dreaming, December 13 - January 21, 1987., cuid8997; 113005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Andreu, Jose: slides, resume., undated; cuid8998; 113004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Aone, Toxic, Koor: exhibition, May 1985., cuid8999; 113003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Appropriate Technology Project [see also I. 1. 13], undated; cuid9000; 113002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Appropriate Technology Project: related newpaper clippings., undated; cuid9001; 113001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Art et Industrie: contract, October 16, 1986., cuid9002; 113000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Art for Money Benefit: collecters, December 4, 1986., cuid9003; 112999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Art for Money Benefit: consignment agreements, November - December 1986., cuid9004; 112998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Art for Money Benefit: correspondence, receipts, and notes, November - December 1986., cuid9005; 112997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Art for Money Benefit: price list, November - December 1986 [see also I. 1. 33], cuid9006; 112996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Art Womb., undated; cuid9007; 112995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Artist in residence program., undated; cuid9008; 112994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Artists resumes /Chalfant, Henry, undated; cuid9009; 112993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Barbican Arts Group: proposal, 1985; cuid9010; 112991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Brenner, Leslie: proposal., undated; cuid9011; 112990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Brown, Marion: newspaper article, flyer., undated; cuid9012; 112989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: consignment sheet., undated; cuid9013; 112987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Charles, Andre Pierre: resume, slides, undated; cuid9014; 112985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated; cuid9015; 112984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Richard: resume., undated; cuid9016; 112983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Conde, Richard: resume., undated; cuid9017; 112982 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Corn, Thom: resume., undated; cuid9018; 112981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Cosentino, Steven: slides, resume., undated; cuid9019; 112980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Cummings, Michael: exhibition proposal., undated; cuid9020; 112979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Danceteria, 1985; cuid9021; 112978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Dawson, Morris: resume., undated; cuid9022; 112977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - De Braud, Alberto: resume., undated; cuid9023; 112976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - [Removed to Oversize], undated; cuid9024; 112975 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Dos Santos, Judith: slides, resume., undated; cuid9025; 112974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Dragan Ilic: resume., undated; cuid9026; 112973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - East Village Ladies Salute the Bronx: exhibition, October 24, 1986; cuid9027; 112972 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Eins, Stefan: resume, reviews, others 1986. [see also over oversize, box 22, also I. 1. 20 and III. A. 4. 75 and 75A], cuid9028; 112971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Eins, Stefan: notes on Moda, January 1986., cuid9029; 112970 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Eins, Stefan: exhibition posters, see oversize box 22, undated; cuid9030; 112969 (Box 4, Folder 37A)
    - English, Ron: resume, articles., undated; cuid9031; 112968 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Evans, Andrea: proposal, 1981. [see also over oversize box 22] and Buczak, Brian, cuid9032; 112967 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9033; 112966 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Exhibition, 1981 - 1985 [see also 1. 1. 2 and III. A. 5. 90-93, also pages 20-26 of Finding Guide], cuid9034; 112965 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Exhibition ideas., undated; cuid9035; 112964 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9036; 112963 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Fashion Moda philosophy [see also I. 1. 1A], undated; cuid9037; 112962 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: artist contracts, November 1 - 16, 1985., cuid9038; 112961 (Box 4, Folder 44A)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: artist contracts, November 1 - 16, 1985., cuid9039; 112960 (Box 4, Folder 44B)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: notes, misc., November 1 - 16, 1985., cuid9040; 112959 (Box 4, Folder 44C)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: price list, press release, insurance., undated; cuid9041; 112958 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Fiorucci, group exhibition, undated; cuid9042; 112957 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Five Boroughs Performance Festival, 1984; cuid9043; 112956 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Garrett, Ken: slides, resume., undated; cuid9044; 112955 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Garramone, Richard: slides, resume., undated; cuid9045; 112954 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - German artists., undated; cuid9046; 112953 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Golden Door project, 1986; cuid9047; 112952 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Graham, Robert and Susan Springfield: exhibition, November 30 - December 22, 1985, cuid9048; 112951 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Grami Gallery: Bogota, Columbia, 1985; cuid9049; 112950 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Graupe-Pillard, Grace: announcements., undated; cuid9050; 112949 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Headley, Wendell E.: resume., undated; cuid9051; 112948 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Haimsohn, Jane: see III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9052; 112947 (Box 4, Folder 54A)
    - Hertz, Betti-Sue: announcement., undated; cuid9053; 112946 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Hochmuth, Rosemarie: catalog, 1986; cuid9054; 112945 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Hsieh, Tehching: proposal, 1985-1986; cuid9055; 112944 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Invitational 1986/87: exhibition., 1986-1987; cuid9056; 112943 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Jackson, Isaac: problem, 1985; cuid9057; 112942 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Januzzi, Angelo: resume, articles., undated; cuid9058; 112941 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Jazz series, 1987; cuid9059; 112940 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Kahane, Lisa:: many slides in III. F. boxes 7-15 and various in III. C. boxes 5 and 6, 1-54, undated; cuid9060; 112939 (Box 4, Folder 61A.)
    - Koor: announcement. {slide at III. A. 4. 36], undated; cuid9061; 112938 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Kush & the Nature Theatre of San Francisco: announcement, mailing list, October, 1986; cuid9062; 112937 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Kaplan, Karen: resume., undated; cuid9063; 112936 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - La Libertad Logico: exhibition, May 17, 1986., cuid9064; 112935 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Legiardi-Laura, Roland: proposal., undated; cuid9065; 112934 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Lehman College, 1987; cuid9066; 112933 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Levy, Judy: slides, resume, 1986; cuid9067; 112932 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Live Radio at Fashion Moda, April 14, 1983. [audio cassette], cuid9068; 112931 (Box 4, Folder 68a., Cassette 68a., E-records fales_mss091, E-records cuid9068)
      Scope and Contents
      April 14th, 1983 broadcast of Audio Art, in conjunction with the Live Radio at Fashion Moda Audio Art exhibition. The program contains a mix of the artists' tapes submitted to the exhibition. Curator/Producer: Isaac Jackson.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 90 min.
    - Lower Eastside Print Shop., undated; cuid9069; 112930 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Lowinger, Leslie: resume., undated; cuid9070; 112929 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Mainland Poetry., undated; cuid9071; 112928 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Margot, "Images in Cloth"/Leslie Lowinger, April 15 - May 7, 1986., cuid9072; 112927 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Matthews, Joan: resume., undated; cuid9073; 112926 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Matschiner, Kristl: resume, photographs., undated; cuid9074; 112925 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Melamid, Brad: see III. A. 4. 39, undated; cuid9075; 112924 (Box 4, Folder 74A.)
    - MC TV Channel J: "Making Coincidences", a TV series by Stefan Eins application, contract, funding, 1984 -1988. [see III. G. 16], cuid9076; 112923 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - MC TV Channel J: notes, 1983- 1988; cuid9077; 112922 (Box 4, Folder 75a.)
    - Meet the composer., undated; cuid9078; 112921 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9079; 112920 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Meyer, Richard: slides, undated; cuid9080; 112919 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Moda gallery layout, undated; cuid9081; 112918 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Moore,Frank: resume, slides, undated; cuid9082; 112917 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Mudmen: articles, undated; cuid9083; 112916 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Nadel, Jeremy: artist statement, 1987; cuid9084; 112915 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Neumann, Dolores: see III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9085; 112914 (Box 5, Folder 82A.)
    - New improvements, 1985; cuid9086; 112913 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9087; 112912 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Nichols Mural/Print project, 1985 [see also I. 1. 33]., cuid9088; 112911 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Nieves, Hector: photographs., undated; cuid9089; 112910 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Owens, A.: artist statement., undated; cuid9090; 112909 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Poets and Writers / Baraka, Amiri, undated; cuid9091; 112908 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Pollack, Steven: see III. A. 4. 17.., undated; cuid9092; 112907 (Box 5, Folder 88A.)
    - Poppitz, James: c. v., letters of recommendation., undated; cuid9093; 112906 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1981 - 1982. [see also oversize, box 20], cuid9094; 112905 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1983- 1984; cuid9095; 112904 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1985- 1986; cuid9096; 112903 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Pullen, Don: see III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9097; 112902 (Box 5, Folder 93A.)
    - Quinn, Barbara: resume., undated; cuid9098; 112901 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Recchia, Louis, undated; cuid9099; 112900 (Box 5, Folder 94A.)
    - Rehm, Celeste: slides, proposal., undated; cuid9100; 112899 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - RenAva: Christmas cards, undated; cuid9101; 112898 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS exhibition with also Juma Santos "Journey", January 1985., cuid9102; 112897 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS "The Inferno", South-Bronx, 1983-1984; cuid9103; 112896 (Box 5, Folder 97A.)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9104; 112895 (Box 5, Folder 98-101)
    - Roloff, Stephen: "The broken Wall, budget., undated; cuid9105; 112894 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Ryan, Debra Gilbert: slides, resume, 1985; cuid9106; 112893 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Sacchetto, Bruno & Nancy Stout: exhibition, March 18 - April 12, 1986., cuid9107; 112892 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - The Salon: announcement mock-ups, 1986; cuid9108; 112891 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - The Salon: promotional materials, 1986; cuid9109; 112890 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Sanna, Richard & Heidi Staudt: proposal, slides., undated; cuid9110; 112889 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9111; 112888 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - "Science, Art, Design, Invention, Technology, Fantasy": production material for book, 1984. [see also I. 1. 29A and III. A. oversize box 21. 114], cuid9112; 112887 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Schuster, Ilene: resume, catalog., undated; cuid9113; 112886 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9114; 112885 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Slide scripts., undated; cuid9115; 112884 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes: workshop, 1984; cuid9116; 112883 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - South Bronx Show: 6th annual, 1985; cuid9117; 112882 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - South Bronx Show: 7th annual, 1986; cuid9118; 112881 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - South Bronx Show: 8th annual, 1988; cuid9119; 112880 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Spank: artist resume., undated; cuid9120; 112879 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Stout, Nancy: announcement, undated; cuid9121; 112878 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9122; 112877 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - SUNY curate, 1987; cuid9123; 112876 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Telacopy, September 26, 1986., cuid9124; 112875 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Tierney, Trin: III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9125; 112874 (Box 5, Folder 121A)
    - Topical Archeology, proposal., undated; cuid9126; 112873 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Touring exhibitions., undated; cuid9127; 112872 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Vienne in South Bronx, Rosa Hochmuth & Lisi Misena, 1986; cuid9128; 112871 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Wahl, Anita: catalogue, undated; cuid9129; 112870 (Box 5, Folder 124A.)
    - Wenneberg, Teresa: resume, undated; cuid9130; 112869 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Wheeler, Irene: slides, resume, 1986; cuid9131; 112868 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Subseries B: Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements., 112832
    Series III Subseries B, Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements, contains articles, press releases, flyers and announcements for exhibitions at Fashion Moda.
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1979; cuid9132; 112866 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1980; cuid9133; 112865 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1981. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9134; 112864 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1982. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9135; 112863 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1983. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9136; 112862 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1984; cuid9137; 112861 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1985; cuid9138; 112860 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1986; cuid9139; 112859 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1987; cuid9140; 112858 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1988; cuid9141; 112857 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1990- 1993; cuid9142; 112856 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, n. d. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9143; 112855 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Articles written by Joe Lewis., undated; cuid9144; 112854 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Press releases, 1979 - 1983. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9145; 112853 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Press releases, 1984- 1988; cuid9146; 112852 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Press releases, 1990-1993; cuid9147; 112851 (Box 5, Folder 15A)
    - Flyers, 1979. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9148; 112850 (Box 5, Folder 16..)
    - Flyers, 1980. [see also oversize, box 21, cuid9149; 112849 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Flyers, 1981. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9150; 112848 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Flyers, 1982. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9151; 112847 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Flyers, 1983. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9152; 112846 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Flyers, 1984. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9153; 112845 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Flyers, 1985/1986 [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9154; 112844 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Flyers, 1987. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9155; 112843 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Flyers, 1988. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9156; 112842 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Flyers, 1989 - 1991. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9157; 112841 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Flyers, 1992- 1993; cuid9158; 112840 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Flyers, n. d., undated; cuid9159; 112839 (Box 5, Folder 26A.)
    - Flyer mockup, undated; cuid9160; 112838 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Flyers for other galleries. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9161; 112837 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Show announcements, 1980- 1985; cuid9162; 112836 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Show announcements, 1986- 1992; cuid9163; 112835 (Box 5, Folder 30)